Guide to the Sid Ramin Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: West Side Story
  - Subseries VI.1 Scores for Broadway Production
    - Volume 4: "Quintet -Act I, Scene 6" - 37 pages; "I Feel Pretty" - 44 pages; "Gee, Officer Krupke" - 34 pages., (115 Pages Leonard Bernstein - 9 pages of manuscript notes, revisions and additions. Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal - 18 pages of manuscript notes, revisions and additions.) (Box Flat Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Volume 5: "Maria" - 14 pages; "New Balcony Scene" - 42 pages; "America" - 54 pages; "One" -29 pages., (139 Pages Leonard Bernstein - 9 pages of manuscript notes, revisions and additions. Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal - 49 pages of manuscript notes, revisions and additions) (Box Flat Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Prologue, (66Pages 252, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 701)
      [With corrections and additions in red, green, and blue pencil by Leonard Bernstein, Sid Ramin, and Irwin Kostal. ]
    - Prologue, (66 Pages 252, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 701)
    - Overture, (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - Jet Song, (36 Pages 215, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - Something's Coming, (20 Pages 160, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - Something's Coming-Chase, (4 Pages 26, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - Dance Hall Sequence, (51 Pages 198, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - Maria Cha-Cha, (15 Pages 61, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - Maria, (14 Pages 54, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - Balcony Scene, (42 Pages 160, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - America, (56 Pages 223, Bars With corrections and additions in red, green, and blue pencil by Leonard Bernstein, Sid Ramin, and Irwin Kostal. ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - America, (56 Pages 223, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - Cool, (42 Pages 171, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - Cha-Cha Insert (Intro to One), (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - One, (29 Pages 115, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 702)
    - Quintet, (37 Pages 151, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - Rumble, (36 Pages 152, Bars With corrections and additions in red, green, and blue pencil by Leonard Bernstein, Sid Ramin, and Irwin Kostal. ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - Rumble, (36 Pages 152, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - I Feel Pretty, (32 Pages 251, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - Intro to Ballet, (7 Pages 24, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - Ballet Sequence, (52 Pages 209, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - Bridge to Somewhere, (1 Page ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - Gee, Officer Krupke!, (31 Pages 232, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - After Officer Krupke, (2 Pages 7, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - Taunting Scene, (11 Pages 40, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - Finale, (7 Pages 34, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 703)
    - Proofs for Print, 1988, (484 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 704)
  - Subseries VI.2 Motion Picture Scores
    Screenplay by Ernest Lehman, based on the Musical Play "West Side Story" (from a conception by Jerome Robbins). Orchestration by Leonard Bernstein, Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal. Released in 1961.
    - Set of Film Scores, 1960-1961, (443 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 704)
    - Prologue - Parts A, 1, 2 (new), 3 - 9., (99 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 1a)
    - Prologue - Music Breakdown, (Manuscript Part 1, 4, and 6. Notes and sketches by Leonard Bernstein) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 1b)
    - Prologue - Part 6 (Sync points from music editor), (5 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 704)
    - Overture, (37 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Quintet, (37 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Mambo, (19 Pages With manuscript notes by Johnny Green.) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 4)
    - Mambo, (19 Pages Insert: 9, Pages ) (Box Flat Box 705)
    - The Dance at the Gym., (11 Pages With manuscript notes by Johnny Green) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 5)
    - The Dance at the Gym "Blues", (11 Pages Insert: 3, Pages ) (Box Flat Box 705)
    - Jump., (12 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Promenade, (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 7)
    - Somewhere, (9 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 8)
    - Maria Cha Cha, (6 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 9)
    - Meeting Scene, (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 10)
    - Promenade Reprise, (6 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 11)
    - The Rumble, (19 Pages and Insert: 4, Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 12)
    - One Hand One Heart, (18 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 13)
    - Balcony Scene, (Part I: 24 Pages Part II: 4, Pages ) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 14)
    - Tonight, Part One. - Extension, (12 Pages Reel 8 Part 3: 6 pages. Alternative Version: 6 pages.) (Box Flat Box 267, Folder 15)
    - End Title, (19 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 16)
    - I Feel Pretty - Entr'acte, (48 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 17)
    - Roof Top, (10 Pages Reel 15, Part Two. A long "accordion" print which contains items 19-23 ff. They are attached in sequence.) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 18)
    - He Killed Your Brother, (3 Pages See folder 18 above.) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 19)
    - Killer, Killer, (5 Pages See folder 18 above.) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 20)
    - Arab-Shadows, (7 Pages See folder 18 above.) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 21)
    - Dig It Good, (2 Pages See folder 18 above.) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 22)
    - Thanks, Daddy-O, (10 Pages See folder 18 above.) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 23)
    - Maria Drops Gun, (7 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 24)
    - Tony Dies, (2 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 25)
    - Maria (Coat Over Shoulder), (2 Pages and Revised: 2, Pages ) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 26)
    - Taunting Scene, (11 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 27)
  - Subseries VI.3 Scores for The Sound of West Side Story by the Ramin-Kostal Orchestra
    Four original orchestral scores were arranged and conducted by Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal for the EP recording. The record was produced by RCA Victor in 1958.
    - Cool, (13 Pages 98, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 705)
    - Cool Fugue, (33 Pages 128, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 705)
    - Maria, (7 Pages 51, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 705)
    - Mambo, (20 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 705)
    - RCA Recording (Box Flat Box 706)
  - Subseries VI.4 Miscellaneous
    - Symphonic Suite, (202 Pages West Side Story Symphonic Suite, later called "Symphonic Dances". Composed by Leonard Bernstein, Orchestrated by Sid Rarain and Irwin Kostal, Folio. The original working copy. Two lines of manuscript notes by Leonard Bernstein on the front cover. With 77 pages of copious manuscript notes, additions, revisions and deletions in the hand of Leonard Bernstein. Also extensive manuscript comments and questions regarding the Suite in the hand of Leonard Bernstein. 29 pages of manuscript revisions, additions and deletions in the hands of Sid Ramin and Irwin Kostal) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Piano Score for Seven Songs, (78 Pages The Manuscript Piano Copies. Early versions used for rehearsals: (1) OPENING. - 30 pages. This song was not used in this form. After many changes and deletions it appeared as ""Jet Song"". (2) PROLOGUE. - 16 pages. Leonard Bernstein's manuscript notes on page 12 and insert page 12a. (3) JET SONG. - 17 pages. Leonard Bernstein's manuscript notes on pages 8 and 11. (4) COOL. - 13 pages. Leonard Bernstein's manuscript notes on page 5. (5) I FEEL PRETTY. - 10 pages. (6) A BOY LIKE THAT. - 13 pages. (7) FINALE. - 2 pages. With 35 pages of manuscript notes by orchestrators and others. Parts of the lyrics were revised or deleted in later versions.) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Motion Picture Music Breakdown, Reels 1 - 21, ( 87Pages Music Breakdown Sheets for the entire motion Picture. Manuscript notes throughout by Sid Ramin.) (Box Flat Box 268, Folder 3)
- Series VII: President Kennedy Anniversary
  Original orchestral scores arranged for the inaugural anniversary celebration for President John F. Kennedy, 1963.
  - Overture, (34 Pages 265, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 705)
  - Play-Ons, (7 Pages 24, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - Cast Finale, (6 Pages 45, Bars ) (Box 705)
- Series VIII: New Thresholds in Sound by Sid Ramin and Orchestra
  Original orchestral scores arranged and conducted by Sid Ramin at Webster Hall, New York City for the record. The recording was produced by Jack A. Somer at RCA Victor in 1963 using the Dynagroove system.
  - Strike Up the Band, (21 Pages 167, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 705)
  - Granada, (12 Pages 93, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - The Sweetest Sounds, (12 Pages 95, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - April In Paris, (17 Pages 66, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - Varsity Drag, (22 Pages 172, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - Embraceable You, (15 Pages 58, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - Spring Is Here, (7 Pages 51, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - I Believe In You, (14 Pages 107, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - Life Is Just a Bowl of Cherries, (20 Pages 74, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - Hernando's Hideaway, (13 Pages 95, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - Bewitched, (18 Pages 72, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - RCA Recording (Box 706)
- Series IX: The Big Band Sound of Sid Ramin
  - Blue Tango, (12 Pages 89, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 705)
  - Never on Sunday, (11 Pages 85, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - In the Mood, (15 Pages 117, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - The Syncopated Clock, (13 Pages 102, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - Holiday for Strings, (30 Pages 235, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - April in Portugal, (10 Pages 75, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - The Poor People of Paris, (17 Pages 131, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - Ruby, (11 Pages 86, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - And the Angels Sing, (12 Pages 94, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - The River Kwai March, (11 Pages 85, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - RCA Recording (Box 706)
- Series X: President Johnson Overtures
  Original orchestral scores and piano-conductor music arranged for the inaugural celebration for President Lyndon B. Johnson, 1965.
  - Inaugural Overture [2 copies], (16 Pages 193, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 705)
  - Overture [2 copies], (34 Pages 266, Bars ) (Box 705)
  - Overture Piano-Conductor Music, (19 Pages 266, Bars ) (Box 707)
- Series XI: Mass
  Orchestral and vocal scores for Leonard Bernstein’s Mass, A Theatre Piece for Singers, Players and Dancers. These scores appear to be from a chamber version of Mass with orchestrations by Sid Ramin was produced in 1972. Mass was originally commissioned by Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis for the Opening of the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts in Washington, D.C. on September 8, 1971. It featured text from the Liturgy of the Roman Mass, additional texts by Stephen Schwartz and Leonard Bernstein, and orchestrations by Jonathan Tunick, Hershy Kay, and Leonard Bernstein.
  - I. Devotions Before Mass, (46 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 707)
  - II. First Introit (Rondo), (49 Pages 260, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - III. Second Introit, (9 Pages ) (Box 707)
  - IV. Confession, (41 Pages 318, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - V. Meditation No. 1 (Orchestra), (6 Pages 59, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - VI. Gloria, (33 Pages 263, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - VII. Meditation No. 2 (Orchestra), (6 Pages 55, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - VIII. Epistle: "The Word of the Lord", (23 Pages 91, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - Gospel-Sermon: "God Said", (32 Pages 186, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - X. Credo, (42 Pages 96, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - XI. Meditation No. 3 (De Profundis, Part 1) and XII. Offertory (De Profundis, Part 2), (XI. 7 Pages 57, Bars XII. 14, Pages 59, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - XIII. The Lord's Prayer, (6 Pages 44, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - XVI. Sanctus, (30 Pages 159, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - XV. Angus Dei, (37 Pages 248, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - XVI. Fraction: "Things Get Broken", (54 Pages 322, Bars ) (Box 707)
  - XVII. Pax: Communion ("Secret Songs"), (16 Pages 140, Bars ) (Box 707)
- Series XII: 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue
  "1600 Pennsylvania Avenue" was entitled "A Musical About the Problems of Housekeeping." The book and lyrics were by Alan Jay Laurens with music by Leonard Bernstein. The show was produced by Roger L. Stevens and Robert Whithead by an arrangement with Saint Subber at the Mark Hellinger Theatre. It was directed and choreographed by Gilbert Moses and George Faison with Roland Gagnon serving as musical director. The music was orchestrated by Sid Ramin and Hershy Kay. Produced in Spring 1976.
  - Subseries XII.1 Songs Used for Orchestration
    The original song copies used for the orchestration of the show by Sid Ramin and Hershy Kay. The song copies have corrections and notations by Ramin and Kay. The final two songs do not appear to have been used in the Broadway production. Quarto.
    - Prelude to Act I [2 copies], (5 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 707)
    - Middle "C", (2 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 707)
    - Rehearsing, (11 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 707)
    - Opening - 10 Square Miles and Dove [3 copies], (17 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 707)
    - Potomac Reprise and Nation (Before Welcome Home) [2 copies], (5 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Welcome Home, Miz Adams [2 copies], (4 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Take Care of This House [2 copies], (7 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Nation 1st Reprise (Before Jefferson March) [2 copies], (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - The President Jefferson March [2 copies], (12 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - The President Jefferson March [4 copies], 23 January 1976, (15 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Jefferson Dance Outline, 5 February 1976, (2 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Jefferson Dance, 7 February 1976, (4 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Seena [2 copies], (4 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Musketry (The British Are Coming) [5 copies], (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Sonatina (The British) [2 copies], (20 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Sonatina (The British), 28 January 1976, (23 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Rondo (Sonatina Finale) [5 copies], (7 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Nation 2nd Reprise (After the Burning) [2 copies], (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 708)
    - Lud's Wedding [5 copies], (14 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 709)
    - Lud's Wedding (Version II) [2 copies], (14 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 709)
    - Wedding Dance [4 copies], (8 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 709)
    - Auction I and II [3 copies], (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 709)
    - The Monroviad ("The Mark of a Man") [2 copies], (21 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 709)
    - This Time [2 copies], (12 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 709)
    - We Must Have a Ball [2 copies], (6 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 709)
    - We Must Have a Ball [4 copies], 23 January 1976, (16 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - We Must Have a Ball [3 copies], 28 January 1976, (22 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - Forty Acres, (6 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - Uncle Tom's Funeral "Bright and Black" [4 copies], (14 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - First Lady Sequence (and New "Hail") [2 copies], (26 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - Hail! [2 copies], (9 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - Minstrel Parade [3 copies], (2 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - The Grand Old Party (Minstrel Show) [3 copies], (6 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - Pity the Poor [3 copies], (2 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - Red, White and Blues [2 copies], (2 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - To Make Us Proud, (6 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 710)
    - American Dreaming [3 copies], (11 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
    - It's My Country (Mr. Lincoln) [3 copies], (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
  - Subseries XII.2 Songs Not Used for Orchestration
    The original song copies were written for the show but do not appear to have been orchestrated or used.
    - Me (New Opening) [2 copies], (18 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
    - Reclamation Scene ("Can You Love") [2 copies], (5 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
    - A Star at Noon [2 copies], (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
    - The Switch [2 copies], (31 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
    - We [2 copies], (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
    - What Happened [2 copies], (3 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
  - Subseries XII.3 Bernstein's Fair Copies
    Copies of Leonard Bernstein's songs for the musical. Stamped Property of Amberson Productions.
    - Fair Copies: "Middle C"; "Opening (10 Square Miles and Dove)"; "Welcome Home Miz Adams"; "Take Care of This House"; "The President Jefferson Sunday Luncheon Party March"; "Seena"; "Sonatina (The British)"; "Lud's Wedding"; "Auction I and II"; "The Monroviad (The Mark of a Man"; "This Time"; "We Must Have a Ball"; "Uncle Tom's Funeral (Bright and Black)"; "Hail!"; "The Grand Old Party (Minstrel Show)"; "Philadephia"; "It's My Country"; "Another Kind of Man (Interlude before Breakout)"; "The Breakout"; "The Switch"; "Reclamation Scene (Can You Love)"; "Freedom Song", (156 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
  - Subseries XII.4 Sketches and Dialogue
    Original manuscript sketches by Leonard Berstein and Sid Ramin in preparation of the score. Typed manuscript pages of dialogue from Act I and Act II of the show.
    - Sketches in Leonard Bernstein's Hand: "President's Entrance (Wedding Act I); "Cakewalk Extension and President's Exit (Wedding Act I)"; "I Love This Land (Act II Finale)", (7 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
    - Sketches: "Opening Continuation"; "Take Care of This House"; "Forty Acres and a Mule"; Unidentifed, (7 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
    - Script Pages: Act I and Act II, April 1976, (8 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 711)
  - Subseries XII.5 Scores of Original Orchestrations
    Original orchestrations by Sid Ramin and Hershy Kay with corrections, markings, and notations. The final six scores do not appear to have been used in the Broadway production. Folio.
    - Overture, (32 Pages 145, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Prelude (Act I) [2 copies], (10 Pages 75, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Middle C (Prelude Act I), (10 Pages 75, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Coach Entrance, (2 Pages 8, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Opening, (34 Pages 142, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Opening - 10 Sq. Miles and Dove, (53 Pages 203, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Opening - Dove, (14 Pages 44, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Potomac Reprise and Nation [2 copies], (16 Pages 51, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Potomac - Horses, (1 Page 6, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Nation Underscore, (12 Pages 47, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Welcome Home Miz Adams [2 copies], (16 Pages 51, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Take Care of This House, (23 Pages 67, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - House to Scene, (1 Page 5, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Nation 1st Reprise (Before Jefferson March), (9 Pages 37, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Nation 1st Reprise (After Jefferson March), (9 Pages 37, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Nation 1st Reprise - Revised [2 copies], 20 February 1976, (7 Pages 23, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Jefferson to R.S.V.P. [2 copies], (1 Page 4, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - R.S.V.P. Utility [3 copies], (6 Pages 18, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - The President Jefferson March, (61 Pages 250, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Seena [2 copies], (13 Pages 47, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Musketry, (9 Pages 36, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 712)
    - Sonatina (The British), (75 Pages 235, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 713)
    - Sonatina (The British) [incomplete], April 1976, (28 Pages ) (Box Flat Box 713)
    - Rondo (Sonatina Finale) [2 copies], (20 Pages 73, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 713)
    - Rondo (Sonatina Finale) Recap - Revised, (9 Pages 43, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 713)
    - Intro to 2nd Nation, (1 Page 5, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 713)
    - Nation 2nd Reprise [2 copies], (12 Pages 47, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 713)
    - Lud's Wedding [2 copies], (44 Pages 156, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 713)
    - Wedding Dance [2 copies], (27 Pages 97, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 713)
    - Auction I and II [2 copies], (10 Pages 32, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 713)
    - The Monroviad [3 copies], (68 Pages 222, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 713)
    - Mark of a Man - Reprise, (9 Pages 33, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 714)
    - This Time [2 copies], (44 Pages 174, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 714)
    - We Must Have a Ball [2 copies], (78 Pages 293, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 714)
    - We Must Have a Ball - Revised, (56 Pages 265, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 714)
    - Uncle Tom's Funeral "Bright and Black", (42 Pages 126, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 714)
    - Uncle Tom's Funeral "Bright and Black" - Revised, (39 Pages 80, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 714)
    - Bright and Black (New), (42 Pages 90, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 714)
    - First Lady [2 copies], (90 Pages 348, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 714)
    - Minstrel Parade [2 copies], (9 Pages 27, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Minstrel Parade - Reprise, (7 Pages 21, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - The Grand Old Party (Minstrel Show) [2 copies], (21 Pages 102, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Pity the Poor [2 copies], (5 Pages 20, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Red, White and Blues [2 copies], (8 Pages 25, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Minstrel Exit, (1 Page 4, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Intro to Proud, (5 Pages 14, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - To Make Us Proud - Revised, (17 Pages 50, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Proud - Arthur Revised, 27 April 1976, (8 Pages 25, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Rehearsal - Closing [incomplete], (20 Pages 89, Bars Contains pages 14-34.) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Closing - Revised [incomplete], (29 Pages 125, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Exit Music, (50 Pages 205, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - American Dreaming [2 copies], (44 Pages 127, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Impeachment [incomplete], (5 Pages 38, Bars Missing page 1.) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Lesson Scene, (17 Pages 64, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Mr. Lincoln, (13 Pages 41, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Noodling Before Philadelphia [3 copies], (1 Page ) (Box Flat Box 715)
    - Philadelphia [2 copies], (24 Pages 68, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 715)
- Series XIII: Jerome Robbins' Broadway
  Original orchestral scores by Sid Ramin and William D. Brohn with corrections, markings, and notations. "Jerome Robbins Broadway" was directed and choreographed by Jerome Robbins. The show was produced by The Shubert Organization, Roger Berlind, Suntory International Corporation, Byron Goldman, and Emanuel Azenberg at the Imperial Theatre. It was co-directed by Grover Dave, co-choreographer by Peter Gennaro, and produced in association with PACE Theatrical Group, Inc. Paul Gemignani served as musical director and Scott Frankel handled music continuity.
  - Overture - Dance, 26 January 1989, (32 Pages 126, Bars ) (Box Flat Box 716)
  - Dance Overture (New) [2 copies], (48 Pages 192, Bars ) (Box 716)
  - Overture - Extension, 27 December 1988, (82 Pages 351, Bars ) (Box 716)
  - High Button Shoes, (133 Pages ) (Box 716)
  - It's Comedy Tonight, (60 Pages 422, Bars ) (Box 716)
  - Mister Monotony [2 copies], 9 January 1989, (20 Pages 80, Bars ) (Box 716)
  - On The Town - Opening, (81 Pages 346, Bars ) (Box 716)
  - West Side Story Suite - Prologue, (63 Pages 274, Bars ) (Box 716)
  - West Side Story Suite - Transition Prologue/Dance Hall [2 copies], (3 Pages 11, Bars ) (Box 717)
  - West Side Story Suite - Dance Hall, (53 Pages 206, Bars ) (Box 717)
  - West Side Story Suite - America, (56 Pages 223, Bars ) (Box 717)
  - West Side Story Suite - Cool, (42 Pages 170, Bars ) (Box 717)
  - West Side Story Suite - Rumble, (31 Pages 134, Bars ) (Box 717)
  - West Side Story Suite - Ballet Sequence, (39 Pages 154, Bars ) (Box 717)
  - Ya Got Me, (45 Pages 178, Bars ) (Box 717)
  - Ya Got Me - Bows, (7 Pages 18, Bars ) (Box 717)
  - You Gotta Get a Gimmick [2 copies], (34 Pages 126, Bars ) (Box 717)
  - Gimmick Playoff, (3 Pages 8, Bars ) (Box 717)
- Series XIV: The Red Shoes
  "The Red Shoes" was adapted from the 1948 film "The Red Shoes" by Michael Powell and Emeric Pressburger. The book was by Marsha Norman and music by Jule Styne with lyrics by Marsha Norman and Paul Stryker. The show was produced by Martin Starger, in association with MCA/UNIVERSAL and James M. Nederlander at the George Gershwin Theatre. It was directed by Stanley Donen, choreographed by Lar Lubovitch, and featured musical directions and vocal arrangements by Donald Pippin. The music by orchestrated by Sid Ramin and William D. Brohn. Produced in Winter 1993.
  - Subseries XIV.1 Lead Sheets